Soham, this is not an idea, welcome
friends, in today's video we will talk
about ICICI Life Insurance jobs, there are 220 jobs here,
you can earn more incentives than the salary you get
here, and from here,
apart from incentives, friends, you also get a
chance to travel, this is the
answer, if you want, you can also
apply here by going for an offline walk-in interview,
or else you
can also apply on the phone, I will tell you online how to apply for this,
but other than this, let me
tell you how much will be the salary in this and
how will the job be, okay, I am going to tell you this complete information
in this, I think this
job will be available to you in X-India, as far as you
can see here, there are
Bhosale locations, so I think and Sanjay
Mishra job location sirp, I will
tell you from which locations and how to
apply, but before moving on, I
request that if you have
not subscribed to Atyath channel, then only Gandhiji's
or everyone's, but for the pace that  Every person gets all the
job notifications and first of all you are
told the information about this job
that this is a life insurance job,
any graduate can apply for it,
if you are interested in it,
you have to take a
test there,
first of all let's talk friends, I will tell you
all the details of how to apply for it,
okay now
you can do it from your laptop also, you can do it from your mobile phone
also, so let me tell you
that this is a bit tight job, a little
time job, that's why I am telling you that
if you do it diligently then there will be no penance
and here also the attack is because
sometimes see the puja that is done is 9:25,
go at 9:00 in the morning and go back home,
but this job is not like that, it is
possible that you may have a special time like this,
but sometimes what happens is that suppose
everyone gets some limit, then you
know there is a customer who is calling you at 5 o'clock, the
time is also 5  It's o'clock, but
Pappu, you shouldn't have missed the customer on this occasion. You have to
go there and
cross off the list given to you,
provided you get up there. Friend,
tell me, child, you have to do something before you leave.
Okay, other times, it happens that there's nothing
missing.
Even if you're sitting in a corner, you still get a crush.
You should work diligently.
And here, friends,
I'll tell you how to work for this.
You get it through the proper trading company. Now, here, there's a
taxation from 15 to 15 days.
In this trading, you pay VAT on everything, like foot, etc. There's
no need to bring an afternoon tax layer, but this does
n't happen at every location. When the button starts,
you should ask about the rates there.
Okay, whether there's a plant of officers here
or not, so
Robert doesn't provide any location.
This is another aspect of trading.  I have
taught you everything from A to Z,
still you have some doubts, then you should
clear it right now and after this, when I will
come to you later and when you will
meet the customer, you will get help from the office near you,
how to do this work, go to the field and
act, I will tell you right now
how to do this, so if you want, you can do
this from your phone or from your laptop, you can type ICC
Chief of Rule of B.Com and you will get it there
or if you go to olx.com for job, then
you will get secondary school links on Google,
like if you open it, the second one in
front of you, here at the top
you can see that there is employees, there is
advisor, okay, it may be that the second video
is a little long, but
you will get complete information here,
friends, what will happen to you,
you will get these lipstick shades here,
suppose then this year also what is the minimum here, then by
writing from Rupees 15, the
salary can be more than that, and so here what
You will get this jail,
you should keep in mind that how many days you work,
how many JDS you get or not, it does not
matter to
you, the
company will pay you whatever salary is being offered to you,
but this does not mean that
you will only work as a helper for salary, it is
not like that, you will have to confirm the work
otherwise the company would have
fired his father, so you must definitely do
this experiment every day, given
below, secondly here
and from one option you can do adventure, there is
no salary in it, here you
get commission on the amount you search,
but friends I have seen that
people who are working in advisor are earning a lot of
money, but
you should have some interest in it, only then you can earn a lot of
salary, in the most adventure
you can earn a lot of money, if you
believe me, which one should you go for, then
see friends, if you have a
regular DP from your qualification side, then you should
directly go into it, you will go into employees,
okay, in which
England  Let me go because this is necessary for you, there are
many people who have backlog
or your career is lost, if it is
difficult for them to get a job, then you should go
on an adventure, if you go to Indore then they will
not select you directly, then by going to the
exam you can edit the same
and you
can earn the same salary from here,
if you go to update now then at the
top you suppose I
click on simply here, then as
soon as you click on simply, now
16 pages will open, see here you will see that if the
express location is telling you here
but if you want mutual rivalry or you want it, okay,
you can do it here, you should
not do it, that
break is with a very simple operation here,
which is telling you
here by saying financial service consultant,
okay this will be your definition now
and here also this position is
what happens in brinjal service bank account friends
here and bank insurance this is also bad from lady, you are
going here for interview then
you should do this  You need to be in the bank's channel, there is
no need for you to go out here,
whenever there is news, when a customer calls,
otherwise you will have to stay in the bank itself and
deal with whatever product you have from the interested customer who comes, there is nothing else,
so I said, look here,
you can see that it is
available for mountain locations, if you want, you
can also slide here from your location and it is okay for selection,
then I am
looking for an option here for you to apply, if you
click on apply here,
a form will open in front of you, select that form
and nothing else,
what is your job location here, I opened White Pearl,
here it is Chandika, I
selected it, secondly here
first middle name last name email ID phone
number date of birth and here gender, then
you will have to fill in the answer and submit it here,
what will happen after that friends,
you will be called by this company,
friends, you will be called for interview there from Neend Begum company  If you mix it, you will mix it
51-A, then a message comes,
in most of the raw cases it happens here that
you get mine and after mixing it, when
after your interview on that fennel 125 work phone, you are given the office address, then you
can go there and give it at the beginning of the festival and not this, friends, many
people have joined this company that
you want to eat, it is written in the description below,
go there and check
and play it, then that's all in the next video,
if you like the video then like, share
and subscribe.